{
  "id": "flashcard-english-5-unit-16",
  "title": "Tiếng Anh Lớp 5 - Unit 16",
  "subject": "english",
  "tags": [
    "grade5",
    "unit16",
    "vocab"
  ],
  "description": "Từ vựng Unit 16: Seasons and the weather",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "cold",
      "answer": "lạnh",
      "speak": "cold"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "hot",
      "answer": "nóng",
      "speak": "hot"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "cool",
      "answer": "mát mẻ",
      "speak": "cool"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "warm",
      "answer": "ấm áp",
      "speak": "warm"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "sunny",
      "answer": "có nắng",
      "speak": "sunny"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "dry",
      "answer": "khô",
      "speak": "dry"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "rainy",
      "answer": "có mưa",
      "speak": "rainy"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "snowy",
      "answer": "có tuyết",
      "speak": "snowy"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "humid",
      "answer": "ẩm ướt",
      "speak": "humid"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "spring",
      "answer": "mùa xuân",
      "speak": "spring"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "summer",
      "answer": "mùa hè",
      "speak": "summer"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "autumn",
      "answer": "mùa thu",
      "speak": "autumn"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "winter",
      "answer": "mùa đông",
      "speak": "winter"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "jumper",
      "answer": "áo len chui đầu",
      "speak": "jumper"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "blouse",
      "answer": "áo sơ mi",
      "speak": "blouse"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "trousers",
      "answer": "quần dài",
      "speak": "trousers"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question": "jeans",
      "answer": "quần jeans",
      "speak": "jeans"
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "question": "shorts",
      "answer": "quần ngắn",
      "speak": "shorts"
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "question": "T-shirt",
      "answer": "áo phông",
      "speak": "t-shirt"
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "question": "skirt",
      "answer": "váy",
      "speak": "skirt"
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "question": "coat",
      "answer": "áo khoác",
      "speak": "coat"
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "question": "outfit",
      "answer": "trang phục",
      "speak": "outfit"
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "question": "dress",
      "answer": "váy đầm",
      "speak": "dress"
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "question": "hat",
      "answer": "mũ",
      "speak": "hat"
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "question": "scraf",
      "answer": "khăn quàng cổ",
      "speak": "scraf"
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "question": "climate",
      "answer": "khí hậu",
      "speak": "climate"
    },
    {
      "id": 27,
      "question": "north",
      "answer": "miền bắc",
      "speak": "north"
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "question": "south",
      "answer": "miền nam",
      "speak": "south"
    },
    {
      "id": 29,
      "question": "bloom",
      "answer": "nở hoa",
      "speak": "bloom"
    },
    {
      "id": 30,
      "question": "ideal",
      "answer": "lý tưởng",
      "speak": "ideal"
    }
  ]
}